sfredbook.com 2013-07-08

# Privacy Statement : myredbook

### Privacy Statement

####  Privacy Policy for myredbook.com

Effective Date: 4 April 2007  
Last Updated: 4 April 2007 

**I. General**

A. The operative parties referred to in this policy are myRedBook S.A. and you, the user of this site. 

1\. myRedBook (Seychelles) S.A. is the publisher and operator of the web site www.myredbook.com. Hereinafter referred to as “COMPANY”. When first-person pronouns are used in this Policy, (us, we, our, ours, etc.) these provisions are referring to myRedBook (Seychelles) S.A. d/b/a myredbook.com. Additionally, when the terms “The SITE” or “SITE” are used, these terms refer to myredbook.com. 

2\. You, the User – As the user of this site, this policy will refer to the user as “you” or through any second-person pronouns, such as “yours,” etc. Hereinafter, the user of the site shall be referred to in applicable second person pronouns. B. This Privacy Policy describes how we use information received about you when you visit our SITE or when you subscribe to, or otherwise use our online services. This Policy does not cover any information that we may receive from or about you through channels other than through the use of the SITE. 

**II. Revisions to this Policy  
**We reserve the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. You should periodically check for any modifications of this Policy by re-visiting this web page and using the “refresh” button on your browser. You should note the date of last revision to this Policy, which appears at the top of this Policy. If the “last modified” date remains unchanged after you have clicked the “refresh” button on your browser, you may presume that no changes have been made since the last reading of the policy. A changed “last modified” dates indicates that this Policy has been updated or edited, and the updated or edited version supersedes any prior versions immediately upon posting. 

**III. Personal information that we collect**   
Visitors to our site and services will have differing of interactivity with us depending on whether visitors simply browse our site, or whether they become members. Depending upon your level of interaction, we will collect different information about you. The type of information collected is as follows: 

A. VIP Members - VIP members who pay by credit card, online checking account, 1-900 telephone are prompted to provide their name and billing information through our billing agent, [www.ccbill.com](http://www.ccbill.com/). ccBill is not affiliated with this site and has its own [ccBill Privacy Policy](http://about.ccbill.com/html_forms/privacy_policy-english.html) with which you should familiarize yourself. VIP members who pay by cash or money order are not prompted for any billing information.

B. Registered Members - Registered members are visitors to our site who choose to register to post information in our public forums. Minimal information is sought, and no actual personally identifying information must be submitted in order to become a registered member. Nevertheless, any information entered voluntarily should be considered to be considered public information or information that is publicly available. If you do not wish for information to be made public, you should not enter it into your user profile when registering. 

C. Browsers - Browsers are visitors to the site who never enter into any active data collection pages. Any information gathered from Browsers is also gathered from Posters and Members. This information is restricted to cookies, IP Addresses and Referral URLs, and other passive information gathering devises (explained below). 

**IV. How we collect information from you**

A. Passive Collection – Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's computer for record-keeping purposes. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. 

B. Active Collection – we collect information from you when you complete registration forms to sign up for your membership or to use interactive sections of our Site. We reserve the right to add additional information collection portals from time to time as we see fit. 

**V.  How we use your information**  
The primary use for your information is to provide you with services you have requested and/or paid for. We also use your information to deliver customized services to you. We additionally will use your information for the purposes for which you specifically provide it, for example, to ensure payment for subscription services.

We use cookies to keep track of your user session. That is, once a person logs on the system, a cookie maintains their credentials so that on subsequent requests for information, we do not have to ask again for the user to log in. We also use cookies to store user preferences, for example: A “collapsed” vs. “expanded” view of the message board listing and a timestamp to use when flagging messages as “new.” 

**VI. Special Cases  
**It is our policy not to use or share the personal information about Visitors or Members in ways unrelated to those described in this Policy without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. We may disclose personal information about Visitors or Members when we believe the release is necessary to comply with the law, enforce our User Agreement or Terms and Conditions. or to protect ourselves, our Members, and the general public. We will only provide information to private civil litigants if required to do so by law. We reserve the right to determine how much effort we wish to expend to defend against civil requests for information. 

**VII. Transmittals from Us**  
We do not send unsolicited emails. 

**VIII. Public Forums, Member Directories, and Internal Messaging  
**A. Public Forums. Any information posted to our public forums, chat areas, or classifieds should immediately be considered to be public information. 

B. Member Directories.   
Any information provided in a user profile, member directory, or other related service should be considered to be public information. We do not, cannot, and will not act to maintain the privacy of any information that you provide in any such forum or medium. Your email address is not displayed on any public directory.

C. Internal Messaging.   
We provide an internal messaging system for use between members of our Site. Any information that you send via this internal messaging system while not publicly displayed, is not guaranteed as secure, and as such, should not considered to be private information. 

**IX. Our Commitment to Data Security**  
We employ firewalls and other measures such as data encryption, to protect the transmission of all sensitive end-user information. We make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems. Nevertheless, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party ‘hackers’ from illegally obtaining this information. We take all reasonable measures to prevent such breaches of security, but given the resourcefulness of cybercriminals we are unable to guarantee that our security is 100% breach-proof. You assume the risk of such breaches to the extent that they occur despite our reasonable security measures. 

**X. How to Access or Modify Your Information**   
We offer our Members the opportunity to access or modify information provided during registration. To access or modify such information, go to your profile at <http://www.myredbook.com/db/login.aspx>

**XI. Where to Direct Questions About Our Privacy Policy**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact us at <http://www.myredbook.com/support.aspx> 

myRedBook S.A.  
Anasuya Est #9  
Revolution Ave  
Victoria Mahe, Seychelles 601771
